getbmwparts.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | getBMWparts

We here at Get BMW Parts take your privacy seriously and understand that  privacy concerns are very important to our customers.  We are committed to protecting your personal privacy and we will never sell or distribute your private or personal information to any other parties or organizations.  We follow strict procedures and maintain electronic safeguards to ensure the protection of your personal information.  All personal information submitted through our website is protected by user authentication procedures and updated encryption technologies.  Your information is only accessible by our authorized getBMWparts staff who are required by law to keep your information secure.

### **What Information is Collected?**

The information we learn from visitors helps us to personalize and continually improve our site. You can visit our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself, but we do collect statistics on the amount of traffic and traffic patterns on our site.  Our staff does obtain and retain certain information as you email us directly and whenever you respond to website questions. We may analyze this data for marketing and technical purposes only. 

### **Links to Third Party Sites**

Our site may include links to other web sites that are not under our control. We recommend reviewing their policies before visiting those websites. 

### **Policy Changes**

This policy is subject to change. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on this privacy policy page.  If you have any questions, or just want to talk policy, you're welcome to [Contact Us here](https://www.getbmwparts.com/contact-us).

.
